UNITE Education Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/022 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Industrial Homework -- tape #640, 1 (Box 20)
- Machine Action Project -- tape #678, 2 (Box 20)
- Jobs With Justice -- tape #660, 3 (Box 20)
- Seoul Sweatshops -- tape #659, 4 (Box 20)
- Inside Business -- tape #658, 5 (Box 20)
- Lech Walesa Speech -- tape #667, 6 (Box 20)
- Solidarity Day: many Faces, One Voice -- tape #663, 7 (Box 20)
- A Victory For Workplace Fairness -- tape #662, 8 (Box 20)
- New York Sweatshops -- tape #645, 9 (Box 20)
- Susan Cowell on the Blue Cross -- tape #679, 10 (Box 20)
- Industrial Homeworkers -- tape #657, 11 (Box 20)
- Crackdown on Sweatshops -- tape #644, 12 (Box 20)
- Segment on Sweatshops -- tape #644, 13 (Box 20)
- ILGWU Chorus -- tape #675, 14 (Box 20)
- Relifting of Homework Ban -- tape #656, 15 (Box 20)
- Full Show on Chinatown -- tape #646, 16 (Box 20)
- ILGWU June 1989 Convention -- tape #651, 17 (Box 20)
- Olympic Athletes' Official Outfits -- tape #649, 18 (Box 20)
- Sonia Laracuente Interview/ILGWU -- tape #647, 19 (Box 20)
- Segment of Pymm -- tape #643, 20 (Box 20)
- Segment on Protest of Salvation Army -- tape #642, 21 (Box 20)
- Shame On You: made in USA Store -- tape #648, 22 (Box 20)
- Video of Practice Teaching -- tape #641, 23 (Box 20)
- Solidarity at Eastern -- tape #669, 24 (Box 20)
- On The Level It's Not Free -- tape #668, 25 (Box 20)
- The New Ergonomic Sewing Station -- tape #665, 26 (Box 20)
- Southern Poverty Law Center -- tape #664, 27 (Box 20)
- TC 2 Today -- tape #661, 28 (Box 20)
- NYC Illegal Sweatshops -- tape #650, 29 (Box 20)
- Garment Workers At Home -- tape #638, 30 (Box 20)
- ILGWU at Labor Day Parade -- tape #639, 31 (Box 20)
- Rain Fair Strike Rally -- tape #702, 1 (Box 21)
- Rain Fair Products Boycott -- tape #701, 2 (Box 21)
- Press Release Sunday Mass -- tape #700, 3 (Box 21)
- ATT-CWA Rally -- tape #698, 4 (Box 21)
- A Retailer Visits the Market -- tape #697, 5 (Box 21)
- Segment on Retraining America -- tape #696, 6 (Box 21)
- Babies in the Mill, 7 (Box 21)
- Older Persons Speak Out -- tape #710, 8 (Box 21)
- Rain Fair's ILGWU Kathy Knaus -- tape #704, 9 (Box 21)
- Paulo Freire -- tape #712, 10 (Box 21)
- We Do The Work, Seasons Highlights -- tape #709, 11 (Box 21)
- We Stand Together -- tape #711, 12 (Box 21)
- The Unofficial Dan Quayle -- tape #713, 13 (Box 21)
- Health Care Action Week -- tape #707, 14 (Box 21)
- Torchlight March With ILGWU -- tape #705, 15 (Box 21)
- NY Fashion 1992 -- tape #688, 16 (Box 21)
- Moneyline: Jay Mazur -- tape #687, 17 (Box 21)
- Asia Watch -- tape #684, 18 (Box 21)
- Highlights of 1989 AFL-CIO Convention -- tape #683, 19 (Box 21)
- Silver Needle Awards Ceremony -- tape #682, 20 (Box 21)
- Organized Crime in Garment Center -- tape #695, 21 (Box 21)
- Mayoral Debate -- tape #694, 22 (Box 21)
- Dukakis-Bush Debate -- tape #693, 23 (Box 21)
- ILGWU - News -- tape #724, 24 (Box 21)
- The Assembly Line -- tape #715, 25 (Box 21)
- Labor Day Parade 1990 -- tape #699, 26 (Box 21)
- What's the Cost of Your Blouse? -- tape #726, 27 (Box 21)
- Fire in Chinatown -- tape #686, 28 (Box 21)
- ILGWU Eastern Rally -- tape #685, 29 (Box 21)
- Grandparents Vote Rally - tape #692, 30 (Box 21)
- ILGWU Rally Edited 1992 -- tape #691, 31 (Box 21)
- Made in America -- tape #690, 32 (Box 21)
- Health Care Reform / McNeil-Lehrer, Jan. 15, 1992, 33 (Box 21)
- Health Care Reform -- tape #730, 1 (Box 22)
- No More Bandaids -- tape #734, 2 (Box 22)
- Changing the Way We Work -- tape #746, 3 (Box 22)
- There's Supposed To Be A Law -- tape #743, 4 (Box 22)
- Women Making it Work -- tape #742, 5 (Box 22)
- Sweatshop (CNN) - tape #739, 6 (Box 22)
- A Switch in Time -- tape #737, 7 (Box 22)
- Meeting Tomorrow's Challenges Today -- tape #736, 8 (Box 22)
- One Strike And You're Out -- tape #757, 9 (Box 22)
- Maramount Corporation - tape #755, 10 (Box 22)
- Guatemala Maquilas -- tape #751, 11 (Box 22)
- Decision '92, Clinton Yes -- tape #752, 12 (Box 22)
- Interview With William Gould -- tape #771, 13 (Box 22)
- Segment on Child Labor Laws -- tape #768, 14 (Box 22)
- Segment on Illegal Sweatshops -- tape #754, 15 (Box 22)
- ILGWU/Leslie Fay Labor Dispute, 16 (Box 22)
- Food Experts to the U.S. -- tape #767, 17 (Box 22)
- The Organized -- tape #766, 18 (Box 22)
- On Strike: the History of Local 2 -- tape #758, 19 (Box 22)
- Garment Workers -- tape #765, 20 (Box 22)
- At What Cost? -- tape #764, 21 (Box 22)
- Italics, Episode #52 -- tape #762, 22 (Box 22)
- Employment and the ADA -- tape #761, 23 (Box 22)
- Salt of the Earth -- tape #749, 24 (Box 22)
- The River Ran Red, 25 (Box 22)
- Dying For a Job -- tape #747, 26 (Box 22)
- Beating the Union Busters -- tape #740, 27 (Box 22)
- People Just Like You -- tape #735, 28 (Box 22)
- Mixed Reviews of NAFTA -- tape #729, 29 (Box 22)
- Allan Howard -- tape #732, 30 (Box 22)
- Heaven Will Protect the Working Girl -- tape #728, 31 (Box 22)
- Joining Hands Across the Border -- tape #727, 32 (Box 22)
- Southeastern Conference -- tape #838, 1 (Box 23)
- ACTWU '92 Convention -- tape #837, 2 (Box 23)
- 1993 ACTWU Convention -- tape #839, 3 (Box 23)
- ACTWU/ILGWU Merger -- tape #777, 4 (Box 23)
- Merger Proposal -- tape #779, 5 (Box 23)
- Solidarity Day '91 -- tape #780, 6 (Box 23)
- Senate Hearings -- tape #775, 7 (Box 23)
- World News Tonight -- tape #776, 8 (Box 23)
- ACTWU Convention Highlights -- tape #835, 9 (Box 23)
- ACTWU Midwest Regional Conference -- tape #836, 10 (Box 23)
- Chicano!/Episode 2. The Struggle in the Fields -- tape #829 -- CR14, 11 (Box 23)
- UNITE! -- UN565 -- tape #827, 12 (Box 23)
- Burning the Bill of Rights -- tape #851, 13 (Box 23)
- Report on ACTWU Health-Tex -- tape #850, 14 (Box 23)
- Preventing Nuclear War -- tape #849, 15 (Box 23)
- ACTWU: Free Trade -- tape #848, 16 (Box 23)
- Leslie Fay -- tape #854, 17 (Box 23)
- To Dream -- tape #853, 18 (Box 23)
- Free Trade: Who's Gonna Pay, 19 (Box 23)
- With Babies and Banners -- tape #859, 20 (Box 23)
- Doing as They Can -- tape #858, 21 (Box 23)
- They'll Never Keep Us Down -- tape #857, 22 (Box 23)
- ILGWU Boycott Soho Manufacturers -- tape #856, 23 (Box 23)
- Good Medicine -- tape #855, 24 (Box 23)
- Call Me Sister, Call Me Brother, 1 (Box 24)
- Demonstration Against Unemployment -- tape #904, 2 (Box 24)
- Maria-Here to Stay -- tape #303, 3 (Box 24)
- Segment on Pauline Newman -- tape #880, 4 (Box 24)
- Health & Safety - Erik Framm Interview, 5 (Box 24)
- Silent Danger -- tape #878, 6 (Box 24)
- NBC Nightly News -- tape #877, 7 (Box 24)
- NAFTA Rally -- tape #868, 8 (Box 24)
  Spanish -- MASTER
- Hunger Strikes -- tape #867, 9 (Box 24)
- ACTWU in the South -- tape #876, 10 (Box 24)
- Dry Cleaning Hazards -- tape #870, 11 (Box 24)
- Video Letter of Solidarity -- tape #905, 12 (Box 24)
- K-mart Conference -- tape #902, 13 (Box 24)
- Evy Duty -- tape #901, 14 (Box 24)
- Evy Duty -- tape #901, 15 (Box 24)
- Prison Work Program -- tape #889, 16 (Box 24)
- Clinton Budget -- tape #893, 17 (Box 24)
- CBS: OSHA Story -- tape #890, 18 (Box 24)
- Final Offer -- tape #886, 19 (Box 24)
- ILGWU-Mazur Interviewed -- tape #882, 20 (Box 24)
- Leslie Fay Settlement -- tape #875, 21 (Box 24)
- Labor Laws -- tape #874, 22 (Box 24)
- Segment With Jay Mazur -- tape #873, 23 (Box 24)
- From Bedside to Bargaining Table -- tape #872, 24 (Box 24)
- ACTWU Protests NAFTA at Monsanto, 25 (Box 24)
- Mildred Holder Fights for Her Home -- tape #864, 26 (Box 24)
- New Harvest, Old Shame - tape #922, 1 (Box 25)
- Political Action -- tape #921, 2 (Box 25)
- High Crimes and Misdemeanors -- tape #920, 3 (Box 25)
- Fired Up -- tape #940, 4 (Box 25)
- Workers Literacy -- tape #939, 5 (Box 25)
- ACTWU GGO Demo -- tape #924, 6 (Box 25)
- NBC Nightly News -- tape #925, 7 (Box 25)
- ACTWU United -- tape #916, 8 (Box 25)
- Cavanaugh's Corner -- tape #926, 9 (Box 25)
- Bruce Raynor/ACTWU -- tape #909, 10 (Box 25)
- Caught in the Act -- tape #1134, 11 (Box 25)
- Sweeney Sweatshop Rally -- tape #1151, 12 (Box 25)
- Union Label Spoofs -- tape #923, 13 (Box 25)
- Health-Tex Strike -- tape #938, 14 (Box 25)
- NY Garment Industry -- tape #943, 15 (Box 25)
- Goody's K-mart, 16 (Box 25)
- K-Mart Compilation -- tape #919, 17 (Box 25)
- Committed to Change -- tape #937, 18 (Box 25)
- We Do the Work-Sheinkman Speech -- tape #931, 19 (Box 25)
- Bernie Firestone Death -- tape #929, 20 (Box 25)
- First Northeast Hispanic Labor Conference, 21 (Box 25)
- ACTWU Media Workshop -- tape #927, 22 (Box 25)
- Friends of the DOL -- tape #907, 23 (Box 25)
- Boy Meet World -- tape #975, 1 (Box 26)
- Sweet-Orr Parade -- tape #947, 2 (Box 26)
- Litton -- Tape #946, 3 (Box 26)
- NAFTA -- tape #977, 4 (Box 26)
- Stand Up For Amer.'s Working Fams. -- tape #978, 5 (Box 26)
- North American Knit Workers -- tape #956, 6 (Box 26)
- My Name is Mary Brown -- tape #970, 7 (Box 26)
- Five Points -- tape #980, 8 (Box 26)
- The Final Offer -- tape #976, 9 (Box 26)
- The Global Assembly Line -- tape #974, 10 (Box 26)
- Vanishing Son -- tape #972, 11 (Box 26)
- Free Trade: A National Disaster -- tape #971, 12 (Box 26)
- Lichtenburg/Sheinkman -- tape #963, 13 (Box 26)
- Nike, Inc. In Indonesia -- tape #962, 14 (Box 26)
- Organizing Unions -- tape #960, 15 (Box 26)
- Reshaping Business -- tape #958, 16 (Box 26)
- Change & Diversity -- tape #953, 17 (Box 26)
- Clinton in Louisville -- tape #951, 18 (Box 26)
- The Struggle at Domsey -- tape #955, 19 (Box 26)
- Health-Tex Clothing & Textile Union, 20 (Box 26)
- Goin' Through the Motions -- tape #945, 21 (Box 26)
- The Willmar -- tape #950, 22 (Box 26)
- Health Care -- tape #969, 23 (Box 26)
- 50 Years of Industrial Unionism -- tape #968, 24 (Box 26)
- U.S. A.I.D. Scandal -- tape #965, 25 (Box 26)
- ILGWU, Department of Labor, Hall of Fame, 1993, 26 (Box 26)
- Manhattan Shirt Plant Reopening -- tape #952, 27 (Box 26)
- Labor Day '95 -- tape #987, 1995; 1 (Box 27)
- No Pain, More Gain -- tape #986, 2 (Box 27)
- Women of Hope -- tape #985, 3 (Box 27)
- Discounted Lives -- tape #999, 4 (Box 27)
- Rural America: We Do the Work, 5 (Box 27)
- This Far by Faith, 6 (Box 27)
- Heroes 2, 7 (Box 27)
- Guess Who Pockets the Difference -- tape #993, 8 (Box 27)
- Union Summer -- tape #993, 9 (Box 27)
- Misc. News Clips -- tape #995, 10 (Box 27)
- Cuts -- tape #991, 11 (Box 27)
- Heroes 3: a presentation o f California Working Group, 12 (Box 27)
- Taking Off, 13 (Box 27)
- Not In Our Town, 14 (Box 27)
- New On The Job, 15 (Box 27)
- Justice For Peerless Workers -- tape #990, 16 (Box 27)
- Union Merger-UNITE -- tape - #989, 17 (Box 27)
- Kathie Lee Gifford/Sweatshops -- tape #988, 18 (Box 27)
- Leaving Home - tape #984, 19 (Box 27)
- No Grapes -- tape #983, 20 (Box 27)
- The Big H -- tape #982, 21 (Box 27)
- Daughters of Free Men -- tape #981, 22 (Box 27)
- Biltmore, Homestead, Red's Java House, 23 (Box 27)
- Susan Cowell/UNITE -- tape #1023, 24 (Box 27)
- Hathaway Shirt Factory Closing -- tape #1021, 25 (Box 27)
- Working Families, 26 (Box 27)
- Strikestory, 27 (Box 27)
- Clinton Remarks on Merger -- tape #996, 28 (Box 27)
- Merger -- tape #1050, 1 (Box 28)
- Segment on Wal-Mart -- tape #1049, 2 (Box 28)
- Multiple Descriptions -- tape #1048, 3 (Box 28)
- Steve Nutter/UNITE -- tape #1047, 4 (Box 28)
- The Killing Floor -- tape #1069, 5 (Box 28)
- Ellis Island Documentary -- tape #1072, 6 (Box 28)
- Triangle Shirt Waist Dedication - Empire State Plaza - 3/24/1993 // New York State Dept. of Labor, 7 (Box 28)
- Restoring Employee Rights -- tape #1070, 8 (Box 28)
- Health-Tex Rally (NC) -- tape #1074, 9 (Box 28)
- Internal Organizing Simulations -- tape #1073, 10 (Box 28)
- Solidarity March -- tape #1076, 11 (Box 28)
- Health-Tex Rally (NYC) -- tape #1075, 12 (Box 28)
- Jose Ramirez -- tape #1063, 13 (Box 28)
- Hometown -- tape #1064, 14 (Box 28)
- Back to the Future III -- tape #1060, 15 (Box 28)
- 1995 AFL-CIO Convention Highlights -- tape #1041, 16 (Box 28)
- Secretary Reich -- tape #1045, 17 (Box 28)
- Talkback Live -- tape #1044, 18 (Box 28)
- Segment on Saipan -- tape #1043, 19 (Box 28)
- Misc. Programs -- tape #1052, 20 (Box 28)
- Hable Con Alguien De Confianza -- tape #1054, 21 (Box 28)
  Spanish
- U.S. A.I.D. Press Conference -- tape #1053, 22 (Box 28)
- Pat Buchanan -- tape #1046, 23 (Box 28)
- National Labor Committee -- tape #1042, 24 (Box 28)
- Organizing 1995 ACTWU Convention -- tape #1035, 25 (Box 28)
- Alan Howard, UNITE -- tape #1031, 26 (Box 28)
- Nightline On Homework -- tape #1058, 27 (Box 28)
- Aqui Me Quedo -- tape #1057, 28 (Box 28)
- Hilary Clinton Sews Union Label -- tape #1095, 1 (Box 29)
- Full Show -- tape #1111, 2 (Box 29)
- Gifford Highlights -- tape #1109, 3 (Box 29)
- Would You Cross A Picket Line -- tape #1108, 4 (Box 29)
- ILGWU Convention 1992 -- tape #1080, 5 (Box 29)
- Paycheck Economics -- tape #1079, 6 (Box 29)
- Monterey Mills -- tape #1078, 7 (Box 29)
- Increasing Participation -- tape #1077, 8 (Box 29)
- Union Organizer -- tape #1086, 9 (Box 29)
- Stand Up For A Real Voice ON the Job -- tape #1085, 10 (Box 29)
- ILGWU Report to Convention 1980, 11 (Box 29)
- Multi-Shop: Join in, 12 (Box 29)
- We Won't Back Down -- tape #1107, 13 (Box 29)
- Now Is the Time for Real Change -- tape #1106, 14 (Box 29)
- Class, Politics & Labor Movement -- tape #1104, 15 (Box 29)
- America Needs a Raise, 16 (Box 29)
- Sweatshops/Child Labor -- tape #1126, 17 (Box 29)
- Out At Work -- tape #1098, 18 (Box 29)
- Words/Face -- tape #1123, 19 (Box 29)
- Gifford Highlights -- tape #1109, 20 (Box 29)
- 82nd Anniv. of Triangle Fire -- tape #1114, 21 (Box 29)
- A. Philip Randolph -- tape #1116, 22 (Box 29)
- Remember Mandela -- tape #1121, 23 (Box 29)
- Golden Lands, Working Hands (2 tapes) -- tape #1115, 24 (Box 29)
- Guatemala Sweatshops -- tape #1132, 1 (Box 30)
- Nike Labor Practices - tape #1129, 2 (Box 30)
- Kathie Lee Gifford/Child Labor -- tape #1133, 3 (Box 30)
- Fashion/Sweatshops -- tape #1137, 4 (Box 30)
- Slave Labor -- tape #1136, 5 (Box 30)
- UNITE (Ch.8) -- tape #1146, 6 (Box 30)
- Going Global-GUESS -- tape #1141, 7 (Box 30)
- Sweatshops-Dateline -- tape #1138, 8 (Box 30)
- UNITE Protest Macy's Stores -- tape #1172, 9 (Box 30)
- Sweatshop Protests -- tape #1169, 10 (Box 30)
- UNITE's Protests -- tape #1170, 11 (Box 30)
- Protest at Evansville -- tape #1166, 12 (Box 30)
- GUESS Sweatshops -- tape #1148, 13 (Box 30)
- GUESS Protest - tape #1147, 14 (Box 30)
  MASTER -- Spanish
- UNITE Protest Robinson May -- tape #1168, 15 (Box 30)
- Macy's Sweatshop Protest, Ch.8 -- tape #1158, 16 (Box 30)
- Peerless Clothing/Macy's Rally -- tape #1155, 17 (Box 30)
- Angels with Dirty Faces -- tape #1131, 18 (Box 30)
- PNDC-Anti Sweatshop -- tape #1140, 19 (Box 30)
- Mickey Mouse Goes to Haiti: Walt Disney and the Science of Exploitation -- tape #1142, 20 (Box 30)
- UNITE '95 - tape #1144, 21 (Box 30)
- GUESS At Dillard's -- tape #1144, 22 (Box 30)
- San Jose News Clip -- tape #1157, 23 (Box 30)
- UNITE: Field Rest Cannon - Organizing Drive -- "JUSTICE" -- tape #1190, 1 (Box 31)
- Segment on American Unions - World News Tonight -- 9/5/1994 -- tape #1189, 2 (Box 31)
- ACTWU ADS -- tape #1188, 3 (Box 31)
- The Business News Service With Vision -- tape #1187, 4 (Box 31)
- UNITE - Fieldcrest vs. the Law -- tape #1182, 5 (Box 31)
- America's Victory -- the 1997 UPS Strike -- tape #1195, 6 (Box 31)
- S. Lichtenberg -- NBC Today -- 5/2/1988 -- tape #1186, 7 (Box 31)
- Tultex Captive - Condensed -- tape #1183, 8 (Box 31)
- The Suit War -- CBC Newsworld - Rough cuts -- Aired March 10, 1997 -- tape #1193, 9 (Box 31)
- Postal Hit in Greensboro, NC 7/1997 -- tape #1184, 10 (Box 31)
- UNITE-GUESS Demo 10/31/1997 -- tape #1208, 11 (Box 31)
- Intercontinental Branded Apparel/UNITE! -- Goodell Plant Address -- April 1996 -- tape #1191, 12 (Box 31)
- MultiPlan - Distant Relatives -- tape #1192, 13 (Box 31)
- Across the River with Hedrick Smith -- tape #1194, 14 (Box 31)
- Industrial Homework -- tape #1185, 15 (Box 31)
- UNITE-Texas -- tape #1181, 16 (Box 31)
- UNITE Sweatshop Protest (Boston) -- tape #1180, 17 (Box 31)
- UNITE-Detroit -- tape #1179, 18 (Box 31)
- UNITE-Indianapolis -- tape #1178, 19 (Box 31)
- UNITE-California -- tape #1175, 20 (Box 31)
- UNITE-Chicago -- tape #1174, 21 (Box 31)
- UNITE Protest Lord & Taylor -- tape #1173, 22 (Box 31)
- UNITE-Philadelphia -- tape #1177, 23 (Box 31)
- Kaufmann's Protest -- tape #1176, 24 (Box 31)
- Battle for Hearts and Minds (The) -- tape #1223, 1 (Box 32)
- Downstream Effect (The) - parts 1-3 -- tape #1224, 2 (Box 32)
- Fury in the Land -- tape #1225, 3 (Box 32)
- Zoned for Slavery -- tape #1229, 4 (Box 32)
- Adidas Protest - US Open -- September 7, 1995 -- tape #1227, 5 (Box 32)
- Surviving the bottom line with Hendrick Smith -- tape #1231, 6 (Box 32)
- Power at Work: Building a Teamster Member-to-Member -- tape #1244, 7 (Box 32)
- Feccheimer - Meeting with Boss - Close-Ups - Tape 2 -- 10/1/1998 -- tape #1234, 8 (Box 32)
- UNITE - July 29th - Lobby Day Against Sweatshops -- tape #1233, 9 (Box 32)
  Chinese -- MASTER
- Wichita, Kansas Postal Action -- 11/15/1997 -- tape #1232, 10 (Box 32)
- Fast Track / Gephardt -- tape #1237, 11 (Box 32)
- Good Day New York (WNYW, Ch. 5) / 3-part segment on Sweatshops -- tape #1236, 12 (Box 32)
- Bergen County Meeting -- tape #1235, 13 (Box 32)
- UNITE Protest -- Oct. 4, 1997 -- tape #1218, 14 (Box 32)
- UNITE Protest -- Oct. 4, 1997 -- tape #1217, 15 (Box 32)
- UNITE Protests -- Oct. 4, 1997 -- tape #1216, 16 (Box 32)
- UNITE/Sweatshops -- Nov. 5, 1997 -- tape #1220, 17 (Box 32)
- Garment Union Protest at Post Office -- Sept. 26, 1997 -- tape #1219, 18 (Box 32)
- UNITE Protest -- Oct. 4, 1997 -- tape #1221, 19 (Box 32)
- 1991 Profiles of Excellence -- tape #1228, 20 (Box 32)
- Union Protest at Sol Frank, 21 (Box 32)
- Jesse Jackson -- 1995 UNITE Convention, Miami, Florida -- tape #1238, 22 (Box 32)
- Union Health Center - Animated Tour - March 1998, 23 (Box 32)
- No Meters -- Oct. 4, 1997 -- tape #1222, 24 (Box 32)
- Chipman Union - Election Day -- 7/27/1993 -- tape #1226, 25 (Box 32)
  MATER
- Political Action, 1 (Box 33)
- Jesse Jackson Addresses ACTWU 1990 Convention, 2 (Box 33)
- Political Action, 3 (Box 33)
- ACTWU United, 1993; 4 (Box 33)
  1st MASTER - Uncorrected 4/22/1993
- UNITE and FIGHT, 5 (Box 33)
  Dub - Edited Copy
- ACTWU UNITED -- t/6/1993, 6 (Box 33)
  dub copy
- ACTWU Expose: US AID Scandal, 7 (Box 33)
- 1993 ACTWU Convention Highlights, 8 (Box 33)
  New MASTER
- 3 Spots - Mama -- 7/16/1985, 9 (Box 33)
- Crafted With Pride in USA Council, 10 (Box 33)
- ACTWU #7 -- 9/28/1995, 1 (Box 34)
- UNITE -- #4 -- 6/29/1995, 2 (Box 34)
- UNITE -- #3 -- 6/29/1995, 3 (Box 34)
- ACTWU -- tape #1 -- 6/28/1995, 4 (Box 34)
- ACTWU -- #6, 5 (Box 34)
- ACTWU -- #4 -- 6/28/1995, 6 (Box 34)
- UNITE -- #5 -- 6/29/1995, 7 (Box 34)
- UNITE -- #7 -- 6/29/1995, 8 (Box 34)
- UNITE -- #2 -- 6/29/1995, 9 (Box 34)
- ACTWU -- #8 -- 6/28/1995, 10 (Box 34)
- UNITE - 6/30/1995, 1 (Box 35)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #17 - 6/27/1995, 2 (Box 35)
- ILGWU Day 3 -- #12 -- 6/28/1995, 3 (Box 35)
- UNITE #3 -- 6/29/1995, 4 (Box 35)
- Gov. Mario Cuomo Addresses -- ACTWU 1990 Convention, 5 (Box 35)
- ILGWU #1 -- 6/23/1995, 6 (Box 35)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #19 -- 6/27/1995, 7 (Box 35)
- ACTWU #8 -- 6/28/1995, 8 (Box 35)
- ACTWU #7 -- 6/28/1995, 9 (Box 35)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #16 -- 6/27/1995, 10 (Box 35)
- ACTWU #5 -- 6/28/1995, 11 (Box 35)
- ILGWU Day 3, Tape 8 -- 6/26/1995, 12 (Box 35)
- 1993 ACTWU Conv. (Barbara Kopple), 13 (Box 35)
  SubMaster
- ILG #4 -- 7/17/1990; Jackson Speech, 14 (Box 35)
- 60 Minutes; Nightline; Paying to Lose Our Jobs -- 9/1992, 15 (Box 35)
- 1993 ACTWU Convention - Jesse Jackson, 16 (Box 35)
- ACTWU Convention Highlights 1993 (unedited), 17 (Box 35)
- Jack Sheinkman Keynote Address ACTWU -- 1990 Convention, 18 (Box 35)
- 1993 ACTWU 6th Constitutional Conv. - Convention Highlights, 19 (Box 35)
- ACTWU/ILGWU Merger (Schedule Enclosed), 20 (Box 35)
- ACTWU - Convention Highlights - 1/9/1990, 21 (Box 35)
- ACTWU United -- 4/27/1993 / Barbara Kopple, 22 (Box 35)
  dub -
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #18 -- 6/27/1995, 1 (Box 36)
- ILGWU Day 3 -- #10 -- 6/26/1995, 2 (Box 36)
- UNITE #4 -- 6/29/1995, 3 (Box 36)
- ILGWU Day 2 -- 6/24/1995, 4 (Box 36)
- ILGWU #3 -- 6/23/1995, 5 (Box 36)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #14 -- 6/27/1995, 6 (Box 36)
- ILGWU Day 2 -- #4 -- 6/24/1995, 7 (Box 36)
- UNITE #2 -- 6/29/1995, 8 (Box 36)
- UNITE #1 -- 6/29/1995, 9 (Box 36)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #18 -- 6/27/1995, 10 (Box 36)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #14 -- 6/27/1995, 11 (Box 36)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- #15 -- 6/27/1995, 12 (Box 36)
- UNITE Day 2 -- #1 -- 6/30/1995, 13 (Box 36)
- ILGWU -- Day 4 -- #13 -- 6/27/1995, 14 (Box 36)
- Hearing on Compensation -- 12/1/1954 -- [All the characters in this program are fictitious], 1 (Box 37)
- Potofsky - Mueller, 2 (Box 37)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America -- The Right to Organize for Broadcast - June 11, 1955, 3 (Box 37)
  Chambersberg, PA
- Unlabeled, 4 (Box 37)
- Brenden Sexton - IUD Conference - 1/1959, 5 (Box 37)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America / present Journey From Yesterday, 6 (Box 37)
- Depressed #1, 7 (Box 37)
  handwriting of title on old box not easily read
- Hillman - Award Luncheon - Spring 1956, 8 (Box 37)
- Unlabeled, 9 (Box 37)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 10 (Box 37)
- Mr. Hillman Speeches -- 1) Labors' non Partisan League; 2) Salute to Labor; 3) Why Labor Supports - Pres. Roosevelt, 11 (Box 37)
- Labor & Supreme Court -- Sidney Hillman - 3/8/1937; 10th Anniversary of Amer. Labor Party - Sidney Hillman - WNEW - 5/24/1946, 12 (Box 37)
- What's Happening in Morristown, Tenn., 13 (Box 37)
- Unlabeled, 14 (Box 37)
- Unlabeled, 15 (Box 37)
- Address by Jacob S. Potofsky, 16 (Box 37)
- Report to the people, 17 (Box 37)
- Hillman Communication Awards - Apr. 1956, 18 (Box 37)
- Atlantic City - Educational Dept. Program -- May 12th, 1958, 19 (Box 37)
- Pipeline 309 - Maurer -- 1/7/1959, 20 (Box 37)
- Unlabeled, 21 (Box 37)
- Jacob Potofsky, 22 (Box 37)
- Textile Workers Union of America - - 5/29/1974, 23 (Box 37)
- Hillman Award Luncheon - Apr. 1956, 24 (Box 37)
- Cotton Synthetic Wool & Worsted -- April 1, 1967, 25 (Box 37)
- Our Story a Musical by Local 23-25, ILGWU, 1 (Box 38)
- ILGWU "Susan", Judy and Jammin, and Ramona -- UL343 -- tape #396, 2 (Box 38)
- We Are One - Source Tape --, 3 (Box 38)
- Garment Shop Closings in Chinatown, 4 (Box 38)
- Crafted With Pride -- 10/28/1985, 5 (Box 38)
- Crafted With Pride, 6 (Box 38)
- American Family Celebration, 7 (Box 38)
- Solidarity Day - August 31, 1991, 8 (Box 38)
- Solidarity Day -- 1991, 9 (Box 38)
- Stills from Puerto Rico, 10 (Box 38)
- Stills - ILGWU - Domsey Election, 11 (Box 38)
- Ruth Fashions (surveillance camera) -- HW/SW252 -- tape #294, 1 (Box 39)
- We Are One -- CB266 -- tape #302, 2 (Box 39)
- We Are One (Chinese Version) -- CB267 -- tape #303, 3 (Box 39)
- 1986 Triangle Fire Commemorative Part 2 -- UH321 -- tape #373, 4 (Box 39)
- Trouble on Fashion Ave -- IL319 -- tape #370, 5 (Box 39)
- Cuomo Speech at ILGWU Convention -- PO297 -- tape #346, 6 (Box 39)
- Edelman Speech at ILGWU Convention 1989 -- SS296 -- TAPE #346, 7 (Box 39)
- Industrial Workers -- HW292 -- tape #341, 8 (Box 39)
- ILGWU Campaign for Justice in Brooklyn #2 -- OR295 -- tape #343, 9 (Box 39)
- Garment Industry: Working at Home -- HW290 -- tape #338, 10 (Box 39)
- News Clips - American Family Day Celebrations -- LM293 -- tape #342, 11 (Box 39)
- ILGWU Campaign for Justice in Brooklyn #1 -- OR294 -- tape #343, 12 (Box 39)
- Kamali - ILGWU Protests -- HW/SW288 -- tape #336, 13 (Box 39)
- ILGWU Report to Convention 1983 -- 4/23/1984, 14 (Box 39)
- ILGWU: Report to convention 1983 / Paula Green Inc. Advertising, 15 (Box 39)
  tape #373
- 1986 Triangle Fire Commemorative Part 1 -- UH320 -- tape #372, 16 (Box 39)
- NY is Fashion -- tape #578, 1 (Box 40)
- We Make Jobs -- tape #576, 2 (Box 40)
- ILGWU Fashion Show -- tape #580, 3 (Box 40)